A Guide to the Records of Western State Hospital, 1825-2000
Library of Virginia
- Series I. Administrative Records, 1825-2000., Extent: 77.75 cubic feet of records and 69 volumes.
  - Series I., Subseries D. Correspondence, 1825-1944.
    - Superintendent's Correspondence Files, 1825-1942.
      - Correspondence, 1825-1942.
        - 1858 N-O. (Box 37, Folder 10)
        - 1858 P-Q. (Box 37, Folder 11)
        - 1858 R. (Box 37, Folder 12)
        - 1858 S. (Box 37, Folder 13)
        - 1858 S. (Box 37, Folder 14)
        - 1858 S. (Box 37, Folder 15)
        - 1858 T. (Box 37, Folder 16)
        - 1858 T. (Box 37, Folder 17)
        - 1858 V. (Box 37, Folder 18)
        - 1858 W. (Box 37, Folder 19)
        - 1858 W. (Box 37, Folder 20)
        - 1858 W. (Box 37, Folder 21)
        - 1858 Y-Z. (Box 37, Folder 22)
        - 1859 A. (Box 37, Folder 23)
        - 1859 B. (Box 37, Folder 24)
        - 1859 B. (Box 37, Folder 25)
        - 1859 B. (Box 38, Folder 1)
        - 1859 C. (Box 38, Folder 2)
        - 1859 C. (Box 38, Folder 3)
        - 1859 C. (Box 38, Folder 4)
        - 1859 D. (Box 38, Folder 5)
        - 1859 E. (Box 38, Folder 6)
        - 1859 F. (Box 38, Folder 7)
        - 1859 G. (Box 38, Folder 8)
        - 1859 H. (Box 38, Folder 9)
        - 1859 H. (Box 38, Folder 10)
        - 1859 H. (Box 38, Folder 11)
        - 1859 I-J. (Box 38, Folder 12)
        - 1859 K. (Box 38, Folder 13)
        - 1859 L. (Box 38, Folder 14)
        - 1859 M. (Box 38, Folder 15)
        - 1859 M. (Box 38, Folder 16)
        - 1859 M. (Box 38, Folder 17)
        - 1859 N-O. (Box 38, Folder 18)
        - 1859 P. (Box 38, Folder 19)
        - 1859 P. (Box 38, Folder 20)
        - 1859 P. (Box 38, Folder 21)
        - 1859 R. (Box 38, Folder 22)
        - 1859 R. (Box 38, Folder 23)
        - 1859 S. (Box 39, Folder 1)
        - 1859 S. (Box 39, Folder 2)
        - 1859 S. (Box 39, Folder 3)
        - 1859 T. (Box 39, Folder 4)
        - 1859 T. (Box 39, Folder 5)
        - 1859 V. (Box 39, Folder 6)
        - 1859 W. (Box 39, Folder 7)
        - 1859 W. (Box 39, Folder 8)
        - 1859 Y. (Box 39, Folder 9)
        - 1860 A. (Box 39, Folder 10)
        - 1860 B. (Box 39, Folder 11)
        - 1860 B. (Box 39, Folder 12)
        - 1860 B. (Box 39, Folder 13)
        - 1860 C. (Box 39, Folder 14)
        - 1860 D. (Box 39, Folder 15)
        - 1860 D. (Box 39, Folder 16)
        - 1860 D. (Box 39, Folder 17)
        - 1860 E. (Box 39, Folder 18)
        - 1860 F. (Box 39, Folder 19)
        - 1860 G. (Box 39, Folder 20)
        - 1860 H. (Box 39, Folder 21)
        - 1860 H. (Box 39, Folder 22)
        - 1860 H. (Box 39, Folder 23)
        - 1860 I-J. (Box 39, Folder 24)
        - 1860 K. (Box 39, Folder 25)
        - 1860 L. (Box 39, Folder 26)
        - 1860 M. (Box 40, Folder 1)
        - 1860 M. (Box 40, Folder 2)
        - 1860 N-O. (Box 40, Folder 3)
        - 1860 P. (Box 40, Folder 4)
        - 1860 P. (Box 40, Folder 5)
        - 1860 Q-R. (Box 40, Folder 6)
        - 1860 S. (Box 40, Folder 7)
        - 1860 T-V. (Box 40, Folder 8)
        - 1860 W. (Box 40, Folder 9)
        - 1860 W. (Box 40, Folder 10)
        - 1860 W. (Box 40, Folder 11)
        - 1860 Y. (Box 40, Folder 12)
        - 1861. (Box 40, Folder 13)
        - 1862. (Box 40, Folder 14)
        - 1863. (Box 40, Folder 15)
        - 1864. (Box 40, Folder 16)
        - 1865 A-G. (Box 40, Folder 17)
        - 1865 H-L. (Box 40, Folder 18)
        - 1865 M. (Box 40, Folder 19)
        - 1865 O-P. (Box 40, Folder 20)
        - 1865 R-S. (Box 40, Folder 21)
        - 1865 T-V. (Box 40, Folder 22)
        - 1865 W. (Box 40, Folder 23)
        - 1865 W. (Box 40, Folder 24)
        - 1865 Z. (Box 40, Folder 25)
        - 1866 A-L. (Box 41, Folder 1)
        - 1866 M. (Box 41, Folder 2)
        - 1866 M. (Box 41, Folder 3)
        - 1866 N-O. (Box 41, Folder 4)
        - 1866 P. (Box 41, Folder 5)
        - 1866 P. (Box 41, Folder 6)
        - 1866 Q. (Box 41, Folder 7)
        - 1866 R. (Box 41, Folder 8)
        - 1866 R. (Box 41, Folder 9)
        - 1866 R. (Box 41, Folder 10)
        - 1866 S. (Box 41, Folder 11)
        - 1866 S. (Box 41, Folder 12)
        - 1866 S. (Box 41, Folder 13)
        - 1866 T-V. (Box 41, Folder 14)
        - 1866 W. (Box 41, Folder 15)
        - 1866 W. (Box 41, Folder 16)
        - 1866 W. (Box 41, Folder 17)
        - 1866 Y. (Box 41, Folder 18)
        - 1867 A. (Box 41, Folder 19)
        - 1867 B. (Box 41, Folder 20)
        - 1867 B. (Box 41, Folder 21)
        - 1867 C. (Box 41, Folder 22)
        - 1867 C. (Box 41, Folder 23)
        - 1867 C. (Box 41, Folder 24)
        - 1867 D. (Box 41, Folder 25)
        - 1867 E-G. (Box 42, Folder 1)
        - 1867 H. (Box 42, Folder 2)
        - 1867 H. (Box 42, Folder 3)
        - 1867 I-J. (Box 42, Folder 4)
        - 1867 K. (Box 42, Folder 5)
        - 1867 L. (Box 42, Folder 6)
        - 1867 M. (Box 42, Folder 7)
        - 1867 M. (Box 42, Folder 8)
        - 1867 N-O. (Box 42, Folder 9)
        - 1867 P-Q. (Box 42, Folder 10)
        - 1867 R. (Box 42, Folder 11)
        - 1867 R. (Box 42, Folder 12)
        - 1867 S. (Box 42, Folder 13)
        - 1867 T. (Box 42, Folder 14)
        - 1867 V. (Box 42, Folder 15)
        - 1867 W. (Box 42, Folder 16)
        - 1867 W. (Box 42, Folder 17)
        - 1867 Y-Z. (Box 42, Folder 18)
        - 1868 A. (Box 42, Folder 19)
        - 1868 B. (Box 42, Folder 20)
        - 1868 B. (Box 42, Folder 21)
        - 1868 B. (Box 42, Folder 22)
        - 1868 C. (Box 42, Folder 23)
        - 1868 C. (Box 43, Folder 1)
        - 1868 C. (Box 43, Folder 2)
        - 1868 D. (Box 43, Folder 3)
        - 1868 E. (Box 43, Folder 4)
        - 1868 F. (Box 43, Folder 5)
        - 1868 G. (Box 43, Folder 6)
        - 1868 G. (Box 43, Folder 7)
        - 1868 H. (Box 43, Folder 8)
        - 1868 H. (Box 43, Folder 9)
        - 1868 J. (Box 43, Folder 10)
        - 1868 K. (Box 43, Folder 11)
        - 1868 K. (Box 43, Folder 12)
        - 1868 L. (Box 43, Folder 13)
        - 1868 M. (Box 43, Folder 14)
        - 1868 M. (Box 43, Folder 15)
        - 1868 M. (Box 43, Folder 16)
        - 1868 N-O. (Box 43, Folder 17)
        - 1868 P-Q. (Box 43, Folder 18)
        - 1868 R. (Box 43, Folder 19)
        - 1868 S. (Box 43, Folder 20)
        - 1868 S. (Box 43, Folder 21)
        - 1868 T. (Box 43, Folder 22)
        - 1868 V. (Box 43, Folder 23)
        - 1868 W. (Box 43, Folder 24)
        - 1868 W. (Box 44, Folder 1)
        - 1868 Y-Z. (Box 44, Folder 2)
        - 1868 A. (Box 44, Folder 3)
        - 1868 A. (Box 44, Folder 4)
        - 1869 B. (Box 44, Folder 5)
        - 1869 B. (Box 44, Folder 6)
        - 1869 B. (Box 44, Folder 7)
        - 1869 B. (Box 44, Folder 8)
        - 1869 C. (Box 44, Folder 9)
        - 1869 C. (Box 44, Folder 10)
        - 1869 D. (Box 44, Folder 11)
        - 1869 E. (Box 44, Folder 12)
        - 1869 F. (Box 44, Folder 13)
        - 1869 G. (Box 44, Folder 14)
        - 1869 G. (Box 44, Folder 15)
        - 1869 H. (Box 44, Folder 16)
        - 1869 H. (Box 44, Folder 17)
        - 1869 H. (Box 44, Folder 18)
        - 1869 I-J. (Box 44, Folder 19)
        - 1869 K. (Box 44, Folder 20)
        - 1869 L. (Box 44, Folder 21)
        - 1869 M. (Box 44, Folder 22)
        - 1869 M. (Box 44, Folder 23)
        - 1869 M. (Box 44, Folder 24)
        - 1869 N-O. (Box 44, Folder 25)
        - 1869 P. (Box 44, Folder 26)
        - 1869 P. (Box 44, Folder 27)
        - 1869 R. (Box 44, Folder 28)
        - 1869 S. (Box 45, Folder 1)
        - 1869 S. (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - 1869 T. (Box 45, Folder 3)
        - 1869 U-V. (Box 45, Folder 4)
        - 1869 W. (Box 45, Folder 5)
        - 1869 Y-Z. (Box 45, Folder 6)
        - 1870 A. (Box 45, Folder 7)
        - 1870 B. (Box 45, Folder 8)
        - 1870 B. (Box 45, Folder 9)
        - 1870 B. (Box 45, Folder 10)
        - 1870 B. (Box 45, Folder 11)
        - 1870 B. (Box 45, Folder 12)
        - 1870 C. (Box 45, Folder 13)
        - 1870 C. (Box 45, Folder 14)
        - 1870 C. (Box 45, Folder 15)
        - 1870 D. (Box 45, Folder 16)
        - 1870 E. (Box 45, Folder 17)
        - 1870 F. (Box 45, Folder 18)
        - 1870 G. (Box 45, Folder 19)
        - 1870 G. (Box 45, Folder 20)
        - 1870 H. (Box 45, Folder 21)
        - 1870 H. (Box 45, Folder 22)
        - 1870 H. (Box 45, Folder 23)
        - 1870 I-J. (Box 45, Folder 24)
        - 1870 K. (Box 45, Folder 25)
        - 1870 L. (Box 45, Folder 2)
        - 1870 M. (Box 46, Folder 1)
        - 1870 M. (Box 46, Folder 2)
        - 1870 M. (Box 46, Folder 3)
        - 1870 M. (Box 46, Folder 4)
        - 1870 N-O. (Box 46, Folder 5)
        - 1870 P. (Box 46, Folder 6)
        - 1870 P. (Box 46, Folder 7)
        - 1870 R. (Box 46, Folder 8)
        - 1870 S. (Box 46, Folder 9)
        - 1870 S. (Box 46, Folder 10)
        - 1870 T. (Box 46, Folder 11)
        - 1870 U-V. (Box 46, Folder 12)
        - 1870 W. (Box 46, Folder 13)
        - 1870 W. (Box 46, Folder 14)
        - 1870 Y. (Box 46, Folder 15)
        - 1871 A. (Box 46, Folder 16)
        - 1871 B. (Box 46, Folder 17)
        - 1871 B. (Box 46, Folder 18)
        - 1871 B. (Box 46, Folder 19)
        - 1871 B. (Box 46, Folder 20)
        - 1871 B. (Box 46, Folder 21)
        - 1871 C. (Box 46, Folder 22)
        - 1871 C. (Box 46, Folder 23)
        - 1871 D. (Box 46, Folder 24)
        - 1871 D. (Box 46, Folder 25)
        - 1871 E. (Box 47, Folder 1)
        - 1871 F. (Box 47, Folder 2)
        - 1871 G. (Box 47, Folder 3)
        - 1871 H. (Box 47, Folder 4)
        - 1871 H. (Box 47, Folder 5)
        - 1871 H. (Box 47, Folder 6)
        - 1871 I. (Box 47, Folder 7)
        - 1871 J. (Box 47, Folder 8)
        - 1871 K. (Box 47, Folder 9)
        - 1871 L. (Box 47, Folder 10)
        - 1871 M. (Box 47, Folder 11)
        - 1871 M. (Box 47, Folder 12)
        - 1871 M. (Box 47, Folder 13)
        - 1871 N-O. (Box 47, Folder 14)
        - 1871 P. (Box 47, Folder 15)
        - 1871 P. (Box 47, Folder 16)
        - 1871 Q. (Box 47, Folder 17)
        - 1871 R. (Box 47, Folder 18)
        - 1871 R. (Box 47, Folder 19)
        - 1871 S. (Box 47, Folder 20)
        - 1871 S. (Box 47, Folder 21)
        - 1871 T. (Box 47, Folder 22)
        - 1871 U-V. (Box 47, Folder 23)
        - 1871 W. (Box 47, Folder 24)
        - 1871 W. (Box 47, Folder 25)
        - 1871 Y. (Box 48, Folder 1)
        - 1872 A. (Box 48, Folder 2)
        - 1872 B. (Box 48, Folder 3)
        - 1872 B. (Box 48, Folder 4)
        - 1872 B. (Box 48, Folder 5)
        - 1872 B. (Box 48, Folder 6)
        - 1872 C. (Box 48, Folder 7)
        - 1872 C. (Box 48, Folder 8)
        - 1872 C. (Box 48, Folder 9)
        - 1872 D. (Box 48, Folder 10)
        - 1872 E-F. (Box 48, Folder 11)
        - 1872 G. (Box 48, Folder 12)
        - 1872 H. (Box 48, Folder 13)
        - 1872 H. (Box 48, Folder 14)
        - 1872 I-J. (Box 48, Folder 15)
        - 1872 K. (Box 48, Folder 16)
        - 1872 L. (Box 48, Folder 17)
        - 1872 L. (Box 48, Folder 18)
        - 1872 M. (Box 48, Folder 19)
        - 1872 M. (Box 48, Folder 20)
        - 1872 M. (Box 48, Folder 21)
        - 1872 N-O. (Box 48, Folder 22)
        - 1872 P. (Box 48, Folder 23)
        - 1872 P. (Box 48, Folder 24)
        - 1872 R. (Box 49, Folder 1)
        - 1872 S. (Box 49, Folder 2)
        - 1872 S. (Box 49, Folder 3)
        - 1872 T. (Box 49, Folder 4)
        - 1872 V. (Box 49, Folder 5)
        - 1872 W. (Box 49, Folder 6)
        - 1872 W. (Box 49, Folder 7)
        - 1872 W. (Box 49, Folder 8)
        - 1872 Z. (Box 49, Folder 9)
        - 1873 A. (Box 49, Folder 10)
        - 1873 B-C. (Box 49, Folder 11)
        - 1873 D. (Box 49, Folder 12)
        - 1873 D. (Box 49, Folder 13)
        - 1873 E. (Box 49, Folder 14)
        - 1873 F. (Box 49, Folder 15)
        - 1873 F. (Box 49, Folder 16)
        - 1873 F. (Box 49, Folder 17)
        - 1873 G. (Box 49, Folder 18)
        - 1873 G. (Box 49, Folder 19)
        - 1873 G. (Box 49, Folder 20)
        - 1873 G. (Box 49, Folder 21)
        - 1873 H. (Box 49, Folder 22)
        - 1873 H. (Box 49, Folder 23)
        - 1873 H. (Box 49, Folder 24)
        - 1873 H. (Box 49, Folder 25)
        - 1873 H. (Box 49, Folder 26)
        - 1873 J. (Box 50, Folder 1)
        - 1873 K. (Box 50, Folder 2)
        - 1873 K. (Box 50, Folder 3)
        - 1873 K. (Box 50, Folder 4)
        - 1873 L. (Box 50, Folder 5)
        - 1873 L. (Box 50, Folder 6)
        - 1873 M. (Box 50, Folder 7)
        - 1873 M. (Box 50, Folder 8)
        - 1873 M. (Box 50, Folder 9)
        - 1873 M. (Box 50, Folder 10)
        - 1873 N-O. (Box 50, Folder 11)
        - 1873 P. (Box 50, Folder 12)
        - 1873 P. (Box 50, Folder 13)
        - 1873 P. (Box 50, Folder 14)
        - 1873 R. (Box 50, Folder 15)
        - 1873 S. (Box 50, Folder 16)
        - 1873 S. (Box 50, Folder 17)
        - 1873 S. (Box 50, Folder 18)
        - 1873 T-V. (Box 50, Folder 19)
        - 1873 W. (Box 50, Folder 20)
        - 1873 W. (Box 50, Folder 21)
        - 1873 W. (Box 50, Folder 22)
        - 1873 W. (Box 50, Folder 23)
        - 1874 A. (Box 50, Folder 24)
        - 1874 B. (Box 50, Folder 25)
        - 1874 B. (Box 51, Folder 1)
        - 1874 B. (Box 51, Folder 2)
        - 1874 C. (Box 51, Folder 3)
        - 1874 C. (Box 51, Folder 4)
        - 1874 D. (Box 51, Folder 5)
        - 1874 E. (Box 51, Folder 6)
        - 1874 F. (Box 51, Folder 7)
        - 1874 G. (Box 51, Folder 8)
        - 1874 H. (Box 51, Folder 9)
        - 1874 H. (Box 51, Folder 10)
        - 1874 J. (Box 51, Folder 11)
        - 1874 K. (Box 51, Folder 12)
        - 1874 L. (Box 51, Folder 13)
        - 1874 L. (Box 51, Folder 14)
        - 1874 L. (Box 51, Folder 15)
        - 1874 M. (Box 51, Folder 16)
        - 1874 M. (Box 51, Folder 17)
        - 1874 M. (Box 51, Folder 18)
        - 1874 M. (Box 51, Folder 19)
        - 1874 N-O. (Box 51, Folder 20)
        - 1874 P. (Box 51, Folder 21)
        - 1874 R. (Box 51, Folder 22)
        - 1874 S. (Box 51, Folder 23)
        - 1874 S. (Box 51, Folder 24)
        - 1874 T-V. (Box 51, Folder 25)
        - 1874 W. (Box 51, Folder 26)
        - 1874 W. (Box 51, Folder 27)
        - 1875 A. (Box 52, Folder 1)
        - 1875 B. (Box 52, Folder 2)
        - 1875 B. (Box 52, Folder 3)
        - 1875 B. (Box 52, Folder 4)
        - 1875 B. (Box 52, Folder 5)
        - 1875 B. (Box 52, Folder 6)
        - 1875 C. (Box 52, Folder 7)
        - 1875 C. (Box 52, Folder 8)
        - 1875 D. (Box 52, Folder 9)
        - 1875 E. (Box 52, Folder 10)
        - 1875 F. (Box 52, Folder 11)
        - 1875 F. (Box 52, Folder 12)
        - 1875 G. (Box 52, Folder 13)
        - 1875 G. (Box 52, Folder 14)
        - 1875 H. (Box 52, Folder 15)
        - 1875 H. (Box 52, Folder 16)
        - 1875 H. (Box 52, Folder 17)
        - 1875 H. (Box 52, Folder 18)
        - 1875 J. (Box 52, Folder 19)
        - 1875 J. (Box 52, Folder 20)
        - 1875 K. (Box 52, Folder 21)
        - 1875 L. (Box 52, Folder 22)
        - 1875 L. (Box 52, Folder 23)
        - 1875 M. (Box 52, Folder 24)
        - 1875 M. (Box 52, Folder 25)
        - 1875 M. (Box 52, Folder 26)
        - 1875 M. (Box 52, Folder 27)
        - 1875 M. (Box 53, Folder 1)
        - 1875 O. (Box 53, Folder 2)
        - 1875 P. (Box 53, Folder 3)
        - 1875 P. (Box 53, Folder 4)
        - 1875 P. (Box 53, Folder 5)
        - 1875 R. (Box 53, Folder 6)
        - 1875 R. (Box 53, Folder 7)
        - 1875 R. (Box 53, Folder 8)
        - 1875 S. (Box 53, Folder 9)
        - 1875 S. (Box 53, Folder 10)
        - 1875 T. (Box 53, Folder 11)
        - 1875 U. (Box 53, Folder 12)
        - 1875 W. (Box 53, Folder 13)
        - 1875 W. (Box 53, Folder 14)
        - 1875 W. (Box 53, Folder 15)
        - 1875 Y. (Box 53, Folder 16)
        - 1876 A. (Box 53, Folder 17)
        - 1876 B. (Box 53, Folder 18)
        - 1876 B. (Box 53, Folder 19)
        - 1876 B. (Box 53, Folder 20)
        - 1876 B. (Box 53, Folder 21)
        - 1876 B. (Box 53, Folder 22)
        - 1876 C. (Box 53, Folder 23)
        - 1876 C. (Box 53, Folder 24)
        - 1876 D. (Box 53, Folder 25)
        - 1876 E. (Box 53, Folder 26)
        - 1876 F. (Box 53, Folder 27)
        - 1876 G. (Box 54, Folder 1)
        - 1876 G. (Box 54, Folder 2)
        - 1876 H. (Box 54, Folder 3)
        - 1876 H. (Box 54, Folder 4)
        - 1876 J. (Box 54, Folder 5)
        - 1876 K. (Box 54, Folder 6)
        - 1876 L. (Box 54, Folder 7)
        - 1876 M. (Box 54, Folder 8)
        - 1876 M. (Box 54, Folder 9)
        - 1876 M. (Box 54, Folder 10)
        - 1876 N. (Box 54, Folder 11)
        - 1876 O. (Box 54, Folder 12)
        - 1876 P. (Box 54, Folder 13)
        - 1876 R. (Box 54, Folder 14)
        - 1876 R. (Box 54, Folder 15)
        - 1876 S. (Box 54, Folder 16)
        - 1876 S. (Box 54, Folder 17)
        - 1876 S. (Box 54, Folder 18)
        - 1876 T. (Box 54, Folder 19)
        - 1876 U-V. (Box 54, Folder 20)
        - 1876 W. (Box 54, Folder 21)
        - 1876 W. (Box 54, Folder 22)
        - 1876 W. (Box 54, Folder 23)
        - 1876 W. (Box 54, Folder 24)
        - 1877 A. (Box 54, Folder 25)
        - 1877 B. (Box 54, Folder 26)
        - 1877 B. (Box 55, Folder 1)
        - 1877 B. (Box 55, Folder 2)
        - 1877 B. (Box 55, Folder 3)
        - 1877 C. (Box 55, Folder 4)
        - 1877 D. (Box 55, Folder 5)
        - 1877 E. (Box 55, Folder 6)
        - 1877 F. (Box 55, Folder 7)
        - 1877 G. (Box 55, Folder 8)
        - 1877 H. (Box 55, Folder 9)
        - 1877 H. (Box 55, Folder 10)
        - 1877 I-J. (Box 55, Folder 11)
        - 1877 K. (Box 55, Folder 12)
        - 1877 L. (Box 55, Folder 13)
        - 1877 M. (Box 55, Folder 14)
        - 1877 M. (Box 55, Folder 15)
        - 1877 M. (Box 55, Folder 16)
        - 1877 M. (Box 55, Folder 17)
        - 1877 M. (Box 55, Folder 18)
        - 1877 N-O. (Box 55, Folder 19)
        - 1877 P. (Box 55, Folder 20)
        - 1877 R. (Box 55, Folder 21)
        - 1877 S. (Box 55, Folder 22)
        - 1877 S. (Box 55, Folder 23)
        - 1877 S. (Box 55, Folder 24)
        - 1877 T-V. (Box 56, Folder 1)
        - 1877 W. (Box 56, Folder 2)
        - 1877 W. (Box 56, Folder 3)
        - 1878 A-B. (Box 56, Folder 4)
        - 1878 C. (Box 56, Folder 5)
        - 1878 C. (Box 56, Folder 6)
        - 1878 D. (Box 56, Folder 7)
        - 1878 D. (Box 56, Folder 8)
        - 1878 E. (Box 56, Folder 9)
        - 1878 F. (Box 56, Folder 10)
        - 1878 F. (Box 56, Folder 11)
        - 1878 F. (Box 56, Folder 12)
        - 1878 G. (Box 56, Folder 13)
        - 1878 H. (Box 56, Folder 14)
        - 1878 H. (Box 56, Folder 15)
        - 1878 H. (Box 56, Folder 16)
        - 1878 H. (Box 56, Folder 17)
        - 1878 H. (Box 56, Folder 18)
        - 1878 I. (Box 56, Folder 19)
        - 1878 J. (Box 56, Folder 20)
        - 1878 K. (Box 56, Folder 21)
        - 1878 K. (Box 56, Folder 22)
        - 1878 K. (Box 56, Folder 23)
        - 1878 L. (Box 56, Folder 24)
        - 1878 L. (Box 57, Folder 1)
        - 1878 M. (Box 57, Folder 2)
        - 1878 M. (Box 57, Folder 3)
        - 1878 M. (Box 57, Folder 4)
        - 1878 N-O. (Box 57, Folder 5)
        - 1878 P. (Box 57, Folder 6)
        - 1878 R. (Box 57, Folder 7)
        - 1878 S. (Box 57, Folder 8)
        - 1878 S. (Box 57, Folder 9)
        - 1878 T. (Box 57, Folder 10)
        - 1878 T. (Box 57, Folder 11)
        - 1878 V. (Box 57, Folder 12)
        - 1878 W. (Box 57, Folder 13)
        - 1878 W. (Box 57, Folder 14)
        - 1878 W. (Box 57, Folder 15)
        - 1878 Y. (Box 57, Folder 16)
        - 1879 A. (Box 57, Folder 17)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 18)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 19)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 20)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 21)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 22)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 23)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 24)
        - 1879 B. (Box 57, Folder 25)
        - 1879 C. (Box 58, Folder 1)
        - 1879 C. (Box 58, Folder 2)
        - 1879 C. (Box 58, Folder 3)
        - 1879 C. (Box 58, Folder 4)
        - 1879 D. (Box 58, Folder 5)
        - 1879 D. (Box 58, Folder 6)
        - 1879 D. (Box 58, Folder 7)
        - 1879 D. (Box 58, Folder 8)
        - 1879 D. (Box 58, Folder 9)
        - 1879 E. (Box 58, Folder 10)
        - 1879 E. (Box 58, Folder 11)
        - 1879 F. (Box 58, Folder 12)
        - 1879 F. (Box 58, Folder 13)
        - 1879 G. (Box 58, Folder 14)
        - 1879 G. (Box 58, Folder 15)
        - 1879 G. (Box 58, Folder 16)
        - 1879 G. (Box 58, Folder 17)
        - 1879 H. (Box 58, Folder 18)
        - 1879 H. (Box 58, Folder 19)
        - 1879 H. (Box 58, Folder 20)
        - 1879 H. (Box 59, Folder 1)
        - 1879 H. (Box 59, Folder 2)
        - 1879 I-J. (Box 59, Folder 3)
        - 1879 J. (Box 59, Folder 4)
        - 1879 K. (Box 59, Folder 5)
        - 1879 L. (Box 59, Folder 6)
        - 1879 L. (Box 59, Folder 7)
        - 1879 L. (Box 59, Folder 8)
        - 1879 L. (Box 59, Folder 9)
        - 1879 M. (Box 59, Folder 10)
        - 1879 M. (Box 59, Folder 11)
        - 1879 M. (Box 59, Folder 12)
        - 1879 M. (Box 59, Folder 13)
        - 1879 M. (Box 59, Folder 14)
        - 1879 N-O. (Box 59, Folder 15)
        - 1879 P. (Box 59, Folder 16)
        - 1879 P. (Box 59, Folder 17)
        - 1879 P. (Box 59, Folder 18)
        - 1879 R. (Box 59, Folder 19)
        - 1879 R. (Box 59, Folder 20)
        - 1879 R. (Box 59, Folder 21)
        - 1879 R. (Box 59, Folder 22)
        - 1879 S. (Box 60, Folder 1)
        - 1879 S. (Box 60, Folder 2)
        - 1879 S. (Box 60, Folder 3)
        - 1879 S. (Box 60, Folder 4)
        - 1879 S. (Box 60, Folder 5)
        - 1879 T. (Box 60, Folder 6)
        - 1879 T. (Box 60, Folder 7)
        - 1879 T. (Box 60, Folder 8)
        - 1879 U-V. (Box 60, Folder 9)
        - 1879 W. (Box 60, Folder 10)
        - 1879 W. (Box 60, Folder 11)
        - 1879 W. (Box 60, Folder 12)
        - 1879 W. (Box 60, Folder 13)
        - 1879 Y. (Box 60, Folder 14)
        - 1880. (Box 60, Folder 15)
        - 1881. (Box 60, Folder 16)
        - 1882. (Box 60, Folder 17)
        - 1883. (Box 60, Folder 18)
        - 1884. (Box 60, Folder 19)
        - 1885. (Box 60, Folder 20)
        - 1886 A. (Box 60, Folder 21)
        - 1886 B. (Box 60, Folder 22)
        - 1886 C. (Box 60, Folder 23)
        - 1886 D. (Box 60, Folder 24)
        - 1886 E-F. (Box 60, Folder 25)
        - 1886 G. (Box 60, Folder 26)
        - 1886 H. (Box 60, Folder 27)
        - 1886 J-L. (Box 61, Folder 1)
        - 1886 M. (Box 61, Folder 2)
        - 1886 N-O. (Box 61, Folder 3)
        - 1886 P. (Box 61, Folder 4)
        - 1886 R-S. (Box 61, Folder 5)
        - 1886 T. (Box 61, Folder 6)
        - 1886 W. (Box 61, Folder 7)
        - 1887 A. (Box 61, Folder 8)
        - 1887 B. (Box 61, Folder 9)
        - 1887 C. (Box 61, Folder 10)
        - 1887 D. (Box 61, Folder 11)
        - 1887 E-G. (Box 61, Folder 12)
        - 1887 H. (Box 61, Folder 13)
        - 1887 I-L. (Box 61, Folder 14)
        - 1887 M. (Box 61, Folder 15)
        - 1887 N-O. (Box 61, Folder 16)
        - 1887 P. (Box 61, Folder 17)
        - 1887 R-T. (Box 61, Folder 18)
        - 1887 W. (Box 61, Folder 19)
        - 1888. (Box 61, Folder 20)
        - 1889. (Box 61, Folder 21)
        - 1890. (Box 61, Folder 22)
        - 1892. (Box 61, Folder 23)
        - 1896-1897. (Box 61, Folder 24)
        - 1898. (Box 61, Folder 25)
        - 1899. (Box 61, Folder 26)
        - 1899. (Box 61, Folder 27)
        - 1900-1904. (Box 61, Folder 28)
        - 1905. (Box 62, Folder 1)
        - 1906 A-L. (Box 62, Folder 2)
        - 1906 M-W. (Box 62, Folder 3)
        - 1907-1909. (Box 62, Folder 4)
        - 1909-1914. (Box 62, Folder 5)
        - 1915-1917. (Box 62, Folder 6)
        - 1918-1922. (Box 62, Folder 7)
        - 1923-1925. (Box 62, Folder 8)